import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const samWQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "What does the word 'dinosaur' mean?",
    options: ["Terrible lizard", "Awful Bird", "Demon of Scales"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "During which era did dinosaurs live?",
    options: ["Paleozoic Era", "Mesozoic Era", "Cenozoic Era"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "What type of diet did Stegosaurus have?",
    options: ["Omnivorous", "Carnivorous", "Herbivorous"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "Which dinosaur is thought to have been the fastest runner?",
    options: ["Allosaurus", "Velociraptor", "Ornithomimus"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "What is the name for meat-eating dinosaurs with hollow bones?",
    options: ["Sauropodomorpha", "Theropods", "Ornithischia"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: "Which dinosaur had the longest known neck?",
    options: ["Mamenchisaurus", "Diplodocus", "Ultrasaurus"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "What type of rock are dinosaur fossils usually found in?",
    options: ["Metamorphic rock", "Sedimentary rock", "Igneous rock"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    question: "How many million years ago did dinosaurs go extinct?",
    options: ["366", "166", "66"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: "What was the average lifespan of a Tyrannosaurus Rex in years?",
    options: ["40", "50", "30"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: "Which large, long-necked dinosaur was one of the biggest plant-eaters?",
    options: ["Omeisaurus", "Brachiosaurus", "Diplodocus"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question: "Which dinosaur had a singular sail-like structure on its back?",
    options: ["Spinosaurus", "Pterodactyl", "Stegosaurus"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: "Which country has the Gobi Desert, famous for dinosaur fossils?",
    options: ["Kyrgyzstan", "China", "Mongolia"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    question: "What is a fossilized dinosaur footprint called?",
    options: ["Implied fossil", "Geographic fossil", "Trace fossil"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question: "What group of animals are dinosaurs' closest living relatives?",
    options: ["Lizards", "Birds", "Snakes"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question: "Which scientist coined the term 'dinosaur'?",
    options: ["John Muir", "Richard Owen", "Theodor Schwann"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
];